Yakando Idol
I'm having a bit of a hard time figuring out what you mean by "it's moving". What does this mean?
I really like to think.
For example, when there is a birthday party, I do it as a solo performer,
I think about what kind of structure I should use for the birthday party,
I think it would be fun to do something like this,
I like to think a lot in my head,
I think a lot, but thinking makes me sleepy.
So I go to sleep to reset myself.
Then I wake up again and think about all kinds of things,
I am also very good at writing things down in memos,
I write things down in a memo, think about them again, and go back to sleep,
I think that is the biggest part of the three major elements in my mind.
Thinking about the birth event, I guess.
At that time, what kind of things do you think about as you watch the event?
What did you think about at that time and what did you output and deliver to the audience?
My birthday event had a definite theme, and what kind of work did you do to help with it? I had a live performance that reflected the process of my transition from high school student to university student,
I would take videos and make them,
I also shoot the videos,
I also make music videos about the struggles I faced when I was in high school,
I would like to make a music video about the struggles I faced when I was in high school,
I would shoot them by myself, and then edit them by myself.
Do you think that comes across well?
You do quite a lot.
Yes, I do. I am pretty good at self-production.
So, I think about how I can make myself known to people,
How can I convey my charm to people who don't know me?
I also like to think about how I can convey my charm to people who don't know me,
I often think about how I can convey my output.
Is producing your own company the most important thing for you right now?
Yes, I would like to work on a group project. I would like to work with groups as well,
But I haven't had much opportunity to do so,
Do you want to be involved with U-PES in the production of live performances?
I have been thinking about it for a long time. I've been thinking about it for a long time,
Also, do you edit your own videos?Also, do you edit your own videos?
Of course I do.
So everyone does their own editing these days?
Yes, they do. I like to take date-style videos of myself rather than vlogs of my board members,
I have my friends take the videos and I edit them,
I'm really good at making it look like we're going out together,
I post the videos on TikTok.
It's amazing. Fukuda-san is like a cyber group,
It's like a cyber group.
It's scary. You can do a lot of different things, and I'm looking forward to seeing how your opinions will expand the range of your live sandclubs and so on.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it. Please visit us.
Is there anything you would like to do for Bukka's live show?
I guess Bukka's live show doesn't have a stage set.
Also, music videos, or opening videos,
There are not many music videos, or opening videos, or anything like that,
So, I try to make the beginning of the song very special,
Also, we try to make a unit corner, not just a song that everyone performs together,
Or, we could use props to play a song,
We should be able to create a production and a song that suits each individual,
The audience wouldn't get tired of watching the show,
I think it would be fun to see new members again.
Do you have such a concrete plan?
I honestly wonder if it won't be long before it comes true. I honestly wonder if it will be too far away,
I hope you will look forward to seeing more live performances.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Do you want to take a picture with this person or do you have a commitment to take a picture with this person?
Do you want to take a picture with this person?
This program is,
This program was provided by Tomohero, Sorashido, Korie, Asaru, and Ban.
Thank you again today.
This program was sent to you courtesy of
Thank you again today!